"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523135","2016-06-08","Scotland Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39476","39476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523136","2016-06-08","Scotland Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39389","39389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523137","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39390","39390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523138","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39406","39406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523139","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many reported personal injury road accidents in each category of severity there were on the M56 between junctions 12 and 14 in each month during the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39492","39492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523140","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39477","39477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523141","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what level of funding was allocated to Department for Transport Incident Support Units serving the M56 between junctions 12 and 14 in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39491","39491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523142","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's press release of 27 March 2015, Government revs up motorcycle market, if he will implement grants for the purchase of electronic motorcycles.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39421","39421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523143","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37977, what estimate his Department has made of future levels of passenger travel (a) to and (b) from Coventry railway station in each of the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39483","39483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523144","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37977, what comparative assessment he has made of trends in the number of passengers travelling from and to (a) Coventry railway station and (b) other stations in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39485","39485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523145","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to increase the number of driving test inspectors based at the Hull testing site so as to ensure a driving test at that site can be booked within one month.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39366","39366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523146","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average wait is for a driving test appointment (a) in England and (b) at the Hull test centre.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39367","39367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523147","2016-06-08","Wales Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39479","39479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523148","2016-06-08","Wales Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39392","39392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523149","2016-06-09","Attorney General","2016-06-06","To ask the Attorney General, what his policy is on the prosecution of women who seek a medical abortion under the Offences Against the Person Act 1861.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39290","39290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523150","2016-06-08","Women and Equalities","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress the Government has made on its women's engagement programme.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39325","39325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523151","2016-06-08","Women and Equalities","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she has taken to implement the Government's policy on increasing the involvement of women's civil society in the development of government policy.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39326","39326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523152","2016-06-08","Women and Equalities","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what criteria the Government uses in deciding which women's organisations to fund; how much funding the Government gave to women's organisations in each of the last three years; and which such organisations received funding from government in each of those years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39327","39327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523153","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of staff in his Department were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39393","39393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523154","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many civil servants in his Department are paid through limited companies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39408","39408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523155","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reason self-employed adoptive parents are excluded from the financial support offered to other workers to allow them to take full leave and settle an adopted child from the care system into their family.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39413","39413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523156","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families in (a) Bristol South constituency and (b) England have re-applied for child benefit for a young person following that person's dropping out of an apprenticeship.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39411","39411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523157","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families in (a) Bristol South constituency and (b) England have had child benefit stopped for a young person because that person took up an apprenticeship.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39412","39412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523158","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on non-payroll staff in his Department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39480","39480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523159","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance appeals his Department conceded prior to their being heard at first-tier tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39455","39455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523160","2016-06-08","Attorney General","2016-06-06","To ask the Attorney General, if he will take steps to offer incentives to encourage more solicitors to offer pro bono work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39508","39508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523161","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of apprenticeship pay rates for young people in supported accommodation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39516","39516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523162","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the expected Resource Accounting and Budgeting charge is for student loans paid out to EU students studying in England.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39517","39517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523163","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what projections have been made of the number of EU students in receipt of student loans likely to be studying in England in (a) 2020, (b) 2030 and (c) 2040.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39518","39518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523164","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what mechanisms there will be under the Apprenticeship Levy for additional support to incentivise employers to take on disadvantaged young people.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39514","39514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523165","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on specific support under the Youth Obligation programme to enable young people with backgrounds of homelessness to access apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39515","39515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523166","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to improve the apprenticeship completion rate of disabled young people.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39529","39529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523167","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department is offering to small and medium-sized enterprises to assist with the cost of setting up an apprenticeship programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39541","39541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523168","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 20 of the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in February 2016, what steps he is taking to oversee implementation of the recommendations of that report.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39546","39546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523169","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 21 of the Housing Act 1988, whether he plans to ensure that private tenants affected by (a) cancer and (b) other long-term health conditions are able to access suitable accommodation, support and protection from eviction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39542","39542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523170","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the Housing and Planning Act 2016 on levels of homelessness in England in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39544","39544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523171","2016-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, following the review of homelessness legislation undertaken by the charity Crisis entitled The homelessness legislation: An independent review of the legal duties owed to homeless people, published on 25 April 2016, whether he plans to undertake a review of such legislation.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39487","39487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523172","2016-06-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many premises in Bolton South East constituency do not have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39547","39547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523173","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the liability is under the 2015-16 Army Readiness Order for the size and deployability requirements of the Challenger 2 Main Battle Tank.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39533","39533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523174","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.37e of the Educational Excellence Everywhere White Paper, when she plans to announce the recipients of the Excellence in Leadership Fund.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39548","39548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523175","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.37e of the Educational Excellence Everywhere White Paper, when she plans to launch the Excellence in Leadership Fund.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39549","39549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523176","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.37e of the Educational Excellence Everywhere White Paper, what the total budget in each year of the Spending Review period will be for the Excellence in Leadership Fund.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39550","39550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523177","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.37e of the Educational Excellence Everywhere White Paper, when she plans to launch the National Teaching Service.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39551","39551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523178","2016-06-09","Department for Education","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.89 of Budget 2016, what progress has been made on Professor Sir Adrian Smith's review of mathematics teaching for 16 to 18 year olds; and when her Department plans to publish the terms of reference for that review.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39545","39545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523179","2016-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's definition is of unabated coal.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39490","39490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523180","2016-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing clear national planning guidelines for the (a) maximum density of shale gas well sites per square mile and (b) minimum distances of such sites from towns and villages.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39523","39523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523181","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government is making on educating young children about rural affairs, animal welfare and how to care responsibly for a pet; in what ways the Government monitors that progress; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39511","39511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523182","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many projects related to freedom of religion of belief are being funded by the Magna Carta Fund for Human Rights and Democracy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39530","39530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523183","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of the appointment of an EU Special Envoy for the promotion of freedom of religion or belief outside the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39531","39531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523184","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of UN Secretary-General's report on Children and Armed Conflict and its Annex, published in April 2016, in which the Saudi-led Coalition is listed as committing grave violations against children in Yemen.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39554","39554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523185","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the UN Secretary-General's report on Children and Armed Conflict, published in April 2016, if his Department will support the immediate establishment of an international, impartial investigation into reported international humanitarian law violations by all parties in the conflict.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39555","39555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523186","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the UN Secretary-General's report on Children and Armed Conflict, published in April 2016, if the Government will suspend arms export licences and reject new applications for arms exports while there is a risk that they could be used in contravention of international humanitarian and human rights laws.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39557","39557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523187","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the UN Secretary-General's report on Children and Armed Conflict, published in April 2016, what steps he is taking to ensure that Saudi Arabia and other Coalition states cooperate with the UN to develop and implement an Action Plan to end and prevent such violations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39556","39556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523188","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will suspend arms export licences and reject new applications for arms exports to any parties that risk using them in contravention of international humanitarian and human rights laws.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39552","39552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523189","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to UN Security Council Resolution 1460, on child soldiers, if he will encourage Saudi Arabia and other states in the Coalition to develop and implement a time-bound action plan to end and prevent violations against children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39553","39553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523190","2016-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which overseas visits by hon. Members have been supported by his Department or by British embassies and consulates in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39537","39537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523191","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made to date on Recommendation 19 of the NHS England Five Year Forward View for Mental Health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39538","39538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523192","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made to date on Recommendation 2 of the NHS England Five Year Forward View for Mental Health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39539","39539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523193","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37371, how many people are in the team with specific responsibility for those areas of policy on children and young people's mental health for which he is accountable.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39540","39540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523194","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical consultations took place in GP practices in the Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group area in the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39558","39558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523195","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total budget is for GPs in (a) Southampton, (b) the Wessex region and (c) England for each of the next five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39561","39561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523196","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP premises in the Southampton local authority area are owned by the NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39562","39562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523197","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of (a) salaries, (b) pension contributions and (c) indemnity costs and other associated costs of running a GP practice.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39563","39563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523198","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps is he taking to make a career in general practice more attractive to medical graduates.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39559","39559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523199","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the NHS England announcement of 21 April 2016 of £2.4 billion additional funding per year for GP care, what proportion of that funding will be allocated to Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39560","39560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523200","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 6 June 2016 to Questions 37441 and 38348, why North Middlesex Hospital is not being supported by the Emergency Care Intensive Support Team via the Emergency Care Improvement Programme.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39536","39536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523201","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will order a review to be undertaken of the administration and operational effectiveness of NHS Property Services in (a) West Sussex and (b) Mid Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39520","39520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523202","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on the potential link between potatoes and high blood pressure.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39502","39502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523203","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce the number of older women having abortions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39503","39503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523204","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential link between drug taking and suicide.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39504","39504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523205","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on encouraging pregnant women to eat fruit.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39505","39505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523206","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37876, what (a) number and (b) proportion of penalty charge notices issued between January and December 2015 related only to medical exemption certificates.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39488","39488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523207","2016-06-09","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37876, what (a) number and (b) proportion of total penalty charge notices issued for invalid medical exemption certificates between January 2015 and December 2015 were subsequently retracted when the patient proved their right to exemption.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39489","39489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523208","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the timeliness of NHS Property Services' (a) agreement and (b) delivery of building works at (i) Sidney West in West Sussex, (ii) Horsham Hospital and (iii) Crawley Hospital.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39512","39512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523209","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued to parents on recommended amounts of sleep for children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39506","39506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523210","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on limiting the amount of time children spend on computers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39507","39507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523211","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the proposals in the European Commission press release, A European Border and Coast Guard to protect Europe's External Borders, IP/15/6327; and if she will estimate the potential effect of those proposals on the budget of the UK Border Force.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39513","39513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523212","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications of the UK leaving the EU on (a) border controls and security and (b) the entry of criminals and terrorists into the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39521","39521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523213","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional coastal patrol vessels she plans to commission.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39532","39532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523214","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish guidance on the Dublin III regulation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39524","39524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523215","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department is on target to resettle 20,000 Syrian refugees by the end of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39522","39522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523216","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of investigations into sexual offences in (a) Wiltshire and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39526","39526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523217","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many applications to appeal a decision on (a) an asylum application and (b) an application for refugee family union in the First Tier Tribunal Asylum and Immigration Chamber the applicant paid a fee in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39525","39525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523219","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her contribution of 4 May 2016, HC Deb Official Report, column 166, whether the unaccompanied children who come to the UK will be eligible to apply for their parents to join them under refugee family reunion rules.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39534","39534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523220","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of Clause 21 of the Bus Services Bill on the ability of Transport for London subsidiaries to bid for local bus service contracts on routes wholly outside of London.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39543","39543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523221","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent changes he has agreed to the rail franchise agreement with Govia Thameslink Railway.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39564","39564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523222","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he or officials of his Department have had with Govia Thameslink Railway on changes to that company's rail franchise.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39565","39565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523223","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which hon. Members were notified about (a) discussions between his Department and Govia Thameslink Railway on changes to that company's rail franchises and (b) changes agreed with that company to those franchises.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39566","39566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523224","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the punctuality record of Govia Thameslink Railway in the last six months.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39567","39567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523225","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has carried out a rural proofing assessment of the likely effects of measures contained in the Bus Services Bill.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39528","39528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523226","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on local authorities creating new municipal bus companies in England.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39527","39527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523227","2016-06-09","Department for Transport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 May 2016 to Question 37933, how much of the £13 billion investment in transport across the North of England referred to in that Answer will be spent on each type of project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39519","39519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523228","2016-06-08","Women and Equalities","2016-06-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will hold discussions with the Secretary of State for Education on encouraging regular trips to engineering firms, factories and laboratories by all-girls' schools to encourage girls to consider STEM careers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39509","39509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523229","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to help older women and men into work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39510","39510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523230","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to encourage businesses to train and employ people with learning difficulties to give them equal opportunities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39535","39535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523428","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to accelerate the rollout of broadband in (a) rural and (b) urban areas.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905305","905305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523432","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of recent trends in (a) the level of and (b) regional variations in the level of domestic tourism.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905289","905289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523864","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on increasing the contribution of creative subjects to children's learning; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905304","905304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524020","2016-06-09","Leader of the House","2016-06-06","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will make it his policy to bring forward proposals on timetabling for Private Members’ Bills","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905331","905331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524128","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support Paralympic sport.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905306","905306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524129","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for funding of broadband provision in Scotland of the UK voting to leave the EU.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905307","905307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524130","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a vote to leave the EU on policies in the Culture White Paper.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905303","905303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522424","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to respond to the Independent review of consumer protection measures concerning online secondary ticketing facilities, published on 26 May 2016; and if he will present his response in a format similar to that of a government response to a select committee report.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38950","38950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522425","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the higher education entry rate data, published in December 2015, what steps his Department is taking to increase the rate of entry to university from young people in (a) Bristol South constituency and (b) other areas that have a low rate of university entry.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38951","38951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522426","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what links firms bidding to run the Land Registry have to offshore tax havens.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38964","38964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522427","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that increases in the number of foreign, high-fee-paying students does not jeopardise access by UK students to places at their local university.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38966","38966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522428","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will hold discussions with major high street retailers on increasing their involvement in local chamber of trade organisations in market towns.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38996","38996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522429","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will hold discussions with major high street retailers on increasing their involvement in local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38997","38997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522430","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's budget allocation was for reducing the number of young people who were classified as not in employment, education or training in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39006","39006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522431","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support third-sector training providers and local authorities in reducing the number of young people who are not in education, employment or training.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39008","39008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522432","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding is available for third-sector training providers to support young people who are not in education, employment or training and not ready for classroom-based learning since the end of the Youth Contract.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39081","39081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522433","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made in improving construction sector productivity since publication of the Government's Productivity Plan in July 2015.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39105","39105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522434","2016-06-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the major barriers his Department has identified are to improving construction productivity; and what steps the Government has taken to remove those barriers.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39106","39106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522435","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will make funding available for discounted or complimentary travel for apprentices.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39133","39133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522436","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) male and (b) female apprentices have undertaken their apprenticeship on a part-time basis in the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39134","39134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522437","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what data his Department collects on a local authority basis on the number of young people classified as (a) not in employment, education or training and (b) unable to be located or unknown.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39141","39141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522438","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices enrolled on a Level 7 (Master's) apprenticeship for (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39169","39169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522439","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many part-time apprenticeships have been taken up in each of the last three years; and what steps he is taking to (a) widen access to apprenticeships and (b) promote the option of part-time apprenticeships.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39187","39187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522440","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will reconsider the proposal to privatise the Land Registry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39188","39188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522441","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answers of 1 June 2016 to Questions 38139 and 38140, how much of the £10.3 million of minimum wage arrears recovered in 2015-16 was recovered from the 85 employers who did not respond to the National Minimum Wage campaign announced by HM Revenue and Customs on 29 July 2015 but were not issued with a Notice of Underpayment and did not have to pay a penalty; and how many workers were identified as having been underpaid by those 85 employers.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39267","39267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522442","2016-06-07","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that postal votes and ballot papers are sent only to eligible voters for the forthcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39266","39266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522443","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of Civil Service Fast Stream employees based in London complete a placement outside London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39272","39272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522444","2016-06-07","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many complaints relating to equal pay were made by (a) male and (b) female employees of government departments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39236","39236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522445","2016-06-07","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's policy is on requiring companies bidding for government contracts to declare their ultimate beneficial ownership before a decision to award such contracts is made.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39208","39208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522446","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 13 April 2016 to Question 32900, what materials have been distributed to (a) students and (b) higher and further education institutions in respect of (i) voter registration and (ii) the EU referendum; what the cost to the public purse of that material was; and if he will place copies of all such material in the Library.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39198","39198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522447","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many migrants from (a) the EU, (b) the EEA and (c) countries outside the EU have settled in the UK since 1 January 2004 in each (i) region and (ii) local authority area where they have settled.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39201","39201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522448","2016-06-07","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government expects to complete its analysis of responses to the consultation on reform of the Civil Service Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39163","39163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522449","2016-06-07","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason the British Virgin Islands were not invited to the UK Anti-Corruption Summit on 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39135","39135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522450","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37839, what the cost to the public purse has been of advertising of the Government's position on the EU referendum specifically on social media to date, excluding the cost of producing, distributing and publicising the Government's EU referendum leaflet and associated website.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39123","39123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522451","2016-06-08","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many births were recorded at (a) West Cumberland Hospital and (b) Cumberland Infirmary, Carlisle in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39010","39010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522452","2016-06-07","Cabinet Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress his Department is making on tackling aggressive fundraising activities by charities.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39053","39053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522453","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that private pension providers facilitate access by policyholders to details of their investments.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38967","38967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522454","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the reasons are for the difference in the figures quoted as payments to HM Treasury in respect of its guarantee for the Mineworkers Pension Scheme and the British Coal Staff Superannuation Scheme in paragraph 1.21 of the National Audit Office report on Department of Trade and Industry: Sale of the mining operations of the British Coal Corporation, HC 360 1995-96, and the Answer of 8 March 2007 to Question 125573, HC Deb, Column 2124W.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38958","38958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522455","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of publishing the leaflets entitled Tax credits: coming to the UK - WTC/FS5 and Social Security abroad: N138.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38979","38979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522456","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37088, which body is responsible for publishing information about funds collected through the Mutual Assistance Recovery Directive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38983","38983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522457","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions the Government has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on widening the provision of real-time sharing of credit information between banks, other major financial institutions and short-term credit providers.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39152","39152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522458","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the HM Treasury analysis: the long term economic impact of EU membership and the alternatives did not include an assessment of the potential effect on the UK economy of a potential reduction in GDP in the EU.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39199","39199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522459","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department plans to take to make young working families aware of ways in which they can access (a) proposed Government schemes in the Lifetime Savings Bill and (b) other Government schemes relating to long-term savings.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39181","39181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522460","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to empower regulators and law enforcement agencies to prevent and detect the laundering of corrupt assets through the UK financial system.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39209","39209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522461","2016-06-08","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will undertake an assessment of the potential effect on the UK economy of a reduction of (a) 0.1, (b) 0.2, (c) 0.3, (d) 0.4, (e) 0.5, (f) one, (g) two, (h) three, (i) four and (j) five per cent in the (i) GDP of each EU member state, (ii) average GDP across the Eurozone and (iii) average GDP across the EU.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39200","39200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522462","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department determined the bands for the soft drinks industry levy; and what scientific studies were used in reaching that decision.","Biography information for Chris Davies","Chris Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39247","39247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522463","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department provides for (a) litter awareness campaigns, (b) implementation of the National Litter Strategy and (c) litter clearance at sites of national and cultural significance.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39270","39270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522464","2016-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what date she plans for the National Litter Strategy to be launched.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39274","39274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522465","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what government funding local litter awareness groups can apply for.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39268","39268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522466","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to bring forward regulations on the testing of electrical installations in rental properties.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39189","39189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522467","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2016 to Question 32596, if he will place in the Library the spreadsheet used to calculate the allocation of the 2016-17 transition grant to individual authorities.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39147","39147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522468","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is his policy to require social housing providers to ensure that a proportion of their properties are adapted for disabled residents.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39068","39068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522469","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 4 May 2016 to Question 33503, in what locations his Department plans to deliver the 400,000 affordable homes referred to in that Answer; and at what level a home will be defined as affordable in (a) London and (b) England.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38980","38980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522470","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2016 to Question 36790, what plans his Department has to review progress under its voluntary agreement with the National Housing Federation and housing associations on replacing homes sold under right-to-buy with new affordable homes.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38981","38981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522471","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to adopt the recommendations made in the Local Plans Expert Group report, published in March 2016.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38988","38988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522472","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the conclusion of the report by the Local Plans Expert Group, published in March 2016, paragraph s15, that local plans in the South East may not enable the full scale of housing need to be met.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38989","38989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522473","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to support young people living at home with their parents in finding their own accommodation.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39079","39079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522474","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been taken into local authority care in each of the last three years as a result of a decision by a local authority that their parents have made themselves intentionally homeless by accruing rent arrears.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38961","38961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522475","2016-06-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the appropriateness of the use by Hertfordshire Local Enterprise Partnership of the £15 million of Growth Deal funds allocated for the purposes of land acquisition.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38970","38970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522476","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policies of the findings of the Independent review of consumer protection measures concerning online secondary ticketing facilities, published on 26 May 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38957","38957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522477","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on whether (a) a person's identity as used to authorise or verify an online account and (b) the fact that a person has such an account should be considered personal data for the purposes of data protection.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38969","38969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522478","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what amount has been invested in grassroots sport in each region and constituent part of the UK in each year since the 2012 London Olympic Games.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38952","38952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522479","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to achieve its goal of a minimum broadband speed of 10Mbps nationwide.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38953","38953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522480","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to prevent online bots being used to purchase hundreds of tickets for concerts and football matches to be sold on a greatly increased prices.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38955","38955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522481","2016-06-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, in what ways the £15 million legacy fund of the Great Exhibition of the North will continue to attract cultural investment in the North.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39132","39132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522482","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with the US government on UK musicians wishing to obtain performance visas for that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39061","39061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522483","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the Great Exhibition of the North on tourism.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39072","39072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522484","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how the £15 million legacy fund for the Great Exhibition of the North will be distributed.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39073","39073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522485","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with (a) the US embassy in London, (b) the US Consulate in Belfast and (c) local councils on allowing UK musicians attempting to obtain visas to the US to conduct visa interviews in their local areas.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39062","39062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522486","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on working together to support musicians in obtaining performance visas for the US.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39063","39063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522487","2016-06-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to ensure that the Information Commissioner's Office and similar organisations do not award pay rises of more than one per cent to senior staff.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39087","39087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522488","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to promote the works of Robert Burns as part of the UK-Russia Year of Language and Literature 2016.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39172","39172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522489","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department and UK Sport will host a UK Sport Gold Series Event at the Olympic Legacy Park in Sheffield.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39179","39179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522490","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made in the transfer of military graves maintained by the Ministry of Defence to the Commonwealth War Graves Commission.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39158","39158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522491","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received of looting by salvage teams of the wreck of HMS Queen Mary which was sunk in the Battle of Jutland; and whether his Department has been presented with any evidence of such looting.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39146","39146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522492","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government has been made aware of involvement of any British nationals in looting of HMS Queen Mary which was sunk in the Battle of Jutland.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39145","39145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522493","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the progress made by NATO since the 2010 Strategic Concept in (a) territorial defence, (b) crisis management and (c) co-operative security.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39103","39103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522494","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14817, what progress the Government plans to make towards nuclear disarmament beyond the steps outlined in the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2010.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39116","39116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522495","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the composition is of a NATO Spearhead Force; and what the UK role and obligation is in such forces.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39102","39102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522496","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to publish the draft statutory instrument on the Veterans Advisory and Pensions Committee; and what consultations he plans to conduct before that draft legislation is published.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39064","39064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522497","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) financial and (b) non-financial support is offered to current and former army personnel affected by mental health problems related to the use of Lariam.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39070","39070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522498","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what stocks of Lariam his Department currently holds.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39071","39071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522499","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the length of time for which UK naval resources will be committed to Operation Sophia.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39020","39020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522500","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of properties in the Married Quarters Estate (i) nationally and (ii) in Greater London are unoccupied; and what rent is paid annually for those properties.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38976","38976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522501","2016-06-08","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-UK airforce personnel were trained by the Royal Air Force in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16; which countries those personnel were from; what the cost to the RAF of such training was; and whether those costs were reimbursed.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39271","39271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522502","2016-06-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37663, if he will provide the hon. Member for Nottingham North with (a) details and (b) copies of the assessment which was used to assess the threats from emerging capabilities to nuclear submarines.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39276","39276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522503","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides on the level of fees a local authority may charge to administer the per nursery pupil payment for the provision of 30 hours free childcare.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39273","39273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522504","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the per pupil fee for the planned introduction of 30 hours free childcare  will be the same for each local authority.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39275","39275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522505","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the number of children in Solihull constituency that would be currently eligible for 30 hours free childcare.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39269","39269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522506","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of (a) private, (b) voluntary and (c) independent nurseries which will provide the additional 15 hours of childcare under the provisions of the Childcare Act 2016.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39245","39245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522507","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with autism in each region attend (a) mainstream schools and (b) specialist provision.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39250","39250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522508","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve provision to meet the educational needs of children with autism.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39217","39217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522509","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average hourly cost per child is to the public purse of the additional 15 hours free childcare provided for under the Childcare Act 2016 in (a) the UK, (b) the North West and (c) Rochdale.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39242","39242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522510","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the (a) likely level of uptake for the extra 15 hour a week childcare provided for under the Childcare Act 2016 and (b) number of people eligible for that extra childcare under the provisions of that Act.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39243","39243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522511","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on including training on autism in initial teacher training.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39218","39218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522512","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Leeds North West constituency and (b) Leeds city region are eligible for 15 hours free childcare.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39055","39055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522513","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from small childcare providers on her plans to increase free childcare entitlement to 30 hours per week and the ability of those providers to fund care places.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39056","39056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522514","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 16 February 2016 to Question 26162, when she plans to publish details of the unspent funding returned to her Department by Luton Girls' Academy or people associated with its free school application.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38982","38982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522515","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to monitor the (a) location and (b) activity of young people under the age of 18 for the purposes of monitoring implementation of the participation age.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39007","39007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522516","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to provide support to parents of children experiencing emotionally-based school refusal.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39083","39083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522517","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the current guidance for schools and local authorities on emotionally-based school refusal; and if her Department will publish distinct statutory guidance on emotionally-based school refusal.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39084","39084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522518","2016-06-08","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 5 May 2016 to Question 35933, on primary education, where the proportion of the teachers and head teachers who supported the principle of the assessment reforms when responding to the 2013 consultation appears in the analysis of consultation responses.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39094","39094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522519","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from local authorities on the ability of those authorities to fund an increase in free childcare entitlement to 30 hours per week.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39057","39057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522520","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to evaluate the pilot schemes on increasing free childcare entitlement to 30 hours per week.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39054","39054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522521","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential financial effect on nurseries in deprived areas of her plans to increase the free childcare entitlement to 30 hours per week.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39058","39058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522522","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils studied GCSE design and technology in (a) England and (b) Wiltshire in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39154","39154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522523","2016-06-07","Department for Education","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of including design and technology in the EBacc.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39157","39157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522524","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will lay before Parliament (a) the Committee on Climate Change report on the compatibility of UK onshore petroleum with meeting UK carbon budgets and (b) her response to that report before 14 June 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39080","39080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522525","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which public appointments (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have approved since May 2015.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39040","39040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522526","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will set out a timeline for consulting on the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39093","39093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522527","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many staff of her Department have been paid off-payroll since May 2015.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39039","39039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522528","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her policy is on making smart meters universally compatible for all energy suppliers.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39050","39050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522529","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with Ofgem on the roll out of smart meters to homes across the UK.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39051","39051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522530","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she has taken to engage with the bidders for the carbon capture and storage competition since its cancellation.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39014","39014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522531","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what payments her Department has made to (a) White Rose CCS, (b) Shell and (c) SSE since the cancellation of the carbon capture and storage competition.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39015","39015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522532","2016-06-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the bidders for the carbon capture and storage competition have (a) sought and (b) been offered compensation from her Department for costs they incurred prior to that competition's cancellation.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39016","39016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522533","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much her Department has spent on agency workers in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39232","39232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522534","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of civil servants in her Department are (a) female and (b) from an ethnic minority.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39231","39231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522535","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on plans by UK companies or organisations to export coal held in UK stockpiles.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39230","39230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522536","2016-06-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many staff in agencies for which she is responsible have been paid off-payroll since May 2015.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39233","39233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522537","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures her Department has in place to record noise nuisance incidents.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39265","39265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522538","2016-06-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what measures are in place to prevent excessive noise from houses in multiple occupation.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39264","39264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522539","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of trends in regular soft drinks sales over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39229","39229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522540","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to encourage other EU member states to implement the Birds and Habitats Directive.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39219","39219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522541","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of the complexity of the rules and requirements for applications under LEADER 5 on the take-up of that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39190","39190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522542","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of soft drinks sales were of (a) regular and (b) diet or low calorie drinks in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39052","39052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522543","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for grants under LEADER 5 North Devon Plus have been (a) received and (b) granted in Torridge and North Devon.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39026","39026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522544","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage recycling.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38978","38978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522545","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's policy is on the appropriateness of the EU sales description of veal as meat of bovine animals aged less than the eight months; and if she will make representations to the EU on changing that description to meat of bovine animals aged less than six months.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39075","39075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522546","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what records the Government maintains on the destinations of greyhounds that are exported abroad for commercial use.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39046","39046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522547","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of animal welfare regulations in (a) Spain, (b) Pakistan, (c) China and (d) other common destination countries for greyhounds exported for commercial use.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39047","39047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522548","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of animals exported abroad for slaughter in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39088","39088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522549","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the extent to which kosher products are sold without being labelled as such in (a) supermarkets and (b) restaurants and cafes.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39092","39092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522550","2016-06-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the extent to which halal products are sold without being labelled as such in (a) supermarkets and (b) restaurants and cafes.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39090","39090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522551","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that the rules and requirements for LEADER 5 do not deter individuals and businesses from pursuing applications under that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39148","39148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522552","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in Bahrain on the health risks to Zainab al-Khawaja and her child in detention; and if he will press for the release of Ms al-Khawaja and her child.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39140","39140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522553","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the President of Malawi on the rise in albinism-related crimes in that country.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39161","39161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522554","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made recent representations to the Ethiopian authorities to secure the release of British citizen Andargachew Tsege from detention in that country.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39178","39178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522555","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Egyptian counterpart on the charging of Mr Mina Thabet with undermining national security.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39194","39194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522556","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he will be raising the case of Andargachew Tsege on his next visit to Ethiopia.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39117","39117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522557","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government plans to request the release of Mr Andargachew Tsege during future Ministerial visits to Ethiopia.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39115","39115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522558","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to sign the Safe Schools Declaration following the World Humanitarian Summit discussions on Education in Emergencies and Protracted Crises held on 23 and 24 May 2016.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39037","39037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522559","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether all powers currently held by the EU will revert to the Government and Parliament in the event of the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38973","38973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522560","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve relations between the UK and Cuba.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38990","38990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522561","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings he had with representatives of the Cuban government during his visit to Cuba in April 2016.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38991","38991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522562","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the bilateral EU-Cuba Political Dialogue and Cooperation Agreement and the end of the common position on UK relations with Cuba.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38992","38992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522563","2016-06-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for (a) Culture, Media and Sport and (b) Business, Innovation and Skills on steps to support UK musicians in obtaining performance visas for the US; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39060","39060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522564","2016-06-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value of trade between the UK and Cuba has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39022","39022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522565","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the number of people defending human rights in Egypt who are under arrest or subject to travel bans, asset freezes or intimidation.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39059","39059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522566","2016-06-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to next visit Ethiopia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39246","39246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522567","2016-06-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 38068, what assessment he has made of the implications for securing the Government's policy objectives at EU level of fewer (a) junior and (b) senior level staff employed in the European Commission who are UK nationals.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39277","39277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522568","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what framework assessment is undertaken when determining the allocation of financial resources to a clinical commissioning group for primary care.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39261","39261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522569","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to fund fibromyalgia research.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39248","39248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522570","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve diagnosis levels for fibromyalgia; and what steps his Department is taking to  increase training for GPs on diagnosis of that condition.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39249","39249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522571","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to introduce (a) video consultations and (b) other new technology into primary care service delivery.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39251","39251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522572","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of UK funding for primary care is spent on BME communities in the Southampton City Council area.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39252","39252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522573","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the funding allocation for GPs in the Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group area is spent on (a) leases and (b) land.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39253","39253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522574","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent per head on GP services in (a) the Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group area, (b) comparator clinical commissioning groups and (c) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39254","39254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522575","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the funding settlement for GPs is for (a) Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group, (b) comparator clinical commissioning groups and (c) England in 2016-17.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39257","39257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522576","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase the number of health professionals who support GPs in the Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group area.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39255","39255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522577","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have benefited from improved access to GP services in the Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group area since the announcement of the Challenge Fund in October 2013.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39256","39256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522578","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group's funding for primary care services was spent on translation services in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39258","39258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522579","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group receives from the public purse; and what that funding is for the (a) highest and (b) lowest funded clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39260","39260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522580","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the advice on mobile telephone safety on the NHS Choices webpages, what the evidence base is for the recommendation that children should only use mobile telephones for essential purposes and keep all calls short.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39204","39204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522581","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with his US counterpart the potential implications for his policies of work undertaken by the US National Toxicology Program on links between mobile telephone use and levels of cancer risk; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39203","39203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522582","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the total NHS budget was spent on translation services in 2015-16; and how much was spent on translation services in each NHS (a) trust and (b) foundation trust in 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39211","39211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522583","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on campaigns to promote the cessation of  smoking in 2015-16; what estimate he has made of planned expenditure by his Department on smoking cessation campaigns in 2016-17; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39228","39228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522584","2016-06-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the effect on human health of glyphosate.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39216","39216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522585","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government has taken to evaluate the effectiveness of the 2014 mental health pilots aimed at helping people with mental health problems back into work.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39215","39215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522586","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much public funding has been provided for research into new alternatives to antibiotics in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39005","39005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522587","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent changes to funding for pharmacies on patient demand for (a) GPs and (b) hospitals in West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39049","39049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522588","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults in (i) Copeland constituency, (ii) Cumbria and (iii) England are classed as (A) overweight, (B) obese and (C) morbidly obese in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39017","39017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522589","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of patients who travelled for 30 minutes or more in an ambulance to access an accident and emergency department in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39025","39025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522590","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that PrescQIPP (a) is accountable for its guidance to clinical commissioning groups and (b) adheres to all appropriate quality standards in its work.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39034","39034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522591","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures his Department has in place to ensure that PrescQIPP is accountable for the safety of its guidance to clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39035","39035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522592","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for applicants to the National Performers List.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38993","38993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522593","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of treatment and support provision available through the NHS for patients of myelodysplastic syndromes blood cancers.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38999","38999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522594","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children in Cumbria have presented at accident and emergency with dental problems in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39011","39011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522595","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many never events have been recorded in hospitals in England in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38974","38974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522596","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 May 2016 to Question 37620, whether the information requested in that Question is collected centrally by the NHS Commissioning Board.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38975","38975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522597","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's policy paper on NHS bursary reform, updated on 7 April 2016, against what baseline number the expected 10,000 increase in nursing, midwifery and allied health training places by 2020 as a result of the replacement of bursaries with student loans has been measured.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38977","38977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522598","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies on funding of training of the findings of the report by London Economics, The impact of the 2015 comprehensive spending review on higher education fees and funding arrangements in subjects allied to medicine, on the potential effect on participation rates in such training of the replacement of bursaries with loans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38971","38971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522599","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the UK Chief Medical Officer's revised alcohol guidelines, published in January 2016.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38959","38959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522600","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will increase funding for research into brain tumours.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38965","38965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522601","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions GPs have issued for Lariam in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39069","39069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522602","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the distance is between two pharmacies that his Department uses to define a cluster.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39074","39074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522603","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of cases of stress and anxiety related to (a) benefit sanctions and (b) conditionality of benefits.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39067","39067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522604","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, where the test sites will be for the planned trials of pre-exposure prophylaxis.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39108","39108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522605","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which organisation has responsibility for commissioning drugs that prevent the contraction of infectious diseases.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39109","39109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522606","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with local businesses on the effect of mandatory displays of hygiene ratings on small, local and rural businesses.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39091","39091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522607","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to review the medical exemption criteria for NHS prescriptions to include all people with long-term conditions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39086","39086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522608","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what safeguards his Department plans to provide to ensure that pharmacies serving (a) deprived and (b) rural areas do not close as a result of changes to funding for community pharmacies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39107","39107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522609","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential link between stopping smoking and obesity levels.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39048","39048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522610","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department took specialist health research into account when undertaking its equality impact assessment on the draft guidance to local housing authorities on the periodical review of housing needs: caravans and houseboats; and what steps his Department is taking to fulfil the UK's international obligations under the National Roma Integration Strategy on addressing the effect of accommodation insecurity on the health of Gypsies and Travellers in Britain.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39186","39186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522611","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37646, what preparatory work NHS England is undertaking on Translarna; and whether a date has been set for a commercial meeting between NHS England and PTC Therapeutics after that preparatory work.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39182","39182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522612","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of the work of the Olympic Legacy Park in Sheffield and the National Centre for Sport and Exercise Medicine to the use of sport and exercise medicine in (a) the NHS and (b) public health practice.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39192","39192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522613","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution to increasing activity levels and tackling long-term health conditions of the work of the Olympic Legacy Park in Sheffield.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39193","39193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522614","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was of emergency admissions for bladder and bowel problems amongst children and young people aged 19 and under in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39156","39156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522615","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to ensure that patients with asthma are referred for specialist treatment after two courses of oral corticosteroids or 12 courses of short-acting beta-agonists.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39167","39167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522616","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of inappropriate referrals to hospital settings for bladder and bowel problems in children and young people aged 19 and under.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39155","39155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522617","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure that applications for Continuing Healthcare are dealt with swiftly and efficiently.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39149","39149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522618","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how guidance on finding pathways of continuous glucose monitoring for people with diabetes is communicated to clinical commissioning groups and people applying for such funding.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39136","39136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522619","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance has been issued for the funding pathways of continuous glucose monitoring for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39137","39137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522620","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England about making Translarna available for use in England.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39151","39151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522621","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to community pharmacy funding on levels of health inequality.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39125","39125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522622","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to funding for community pharmacies on individuals with restricted mobility.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39126","39126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522623","2016-06-08","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to funding for community pharmacies on access to healthcare for deprived communities.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39127","39127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522624","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current (a) manpower establishment and (b) deployment is of the UK Border Force.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39124","39124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522625","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to accelerate the family reunification process for unaccompanied children in Europe with a family in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39139","39139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522626","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places have been made available by each London borough for (a) the Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme, (b) the Children at Risk from the Middle East and North Africa scheme and (c) unaccompanied asylum seeking children in Europe.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39130","39130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522627","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) asylum seekers and (b) refugees have been accommodated by each London borough in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39131","39131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522628","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to accelerate the family reunification process for unaccompanied children in Europe with family members in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39170","39170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522629","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been employed as Prevent coordinators in the last five years; and how many such people are no longer in post.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39183","39183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522630","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average amount of time spent in post was for all Prevent co-ordinators who both began and left employment in the last five years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39180","39180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522631","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that benefit applications by people who have been granted the right to remain in the UK are not affected by the time taken for confirmation of leave to remain.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39197","39197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522632","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the regulation of the private security industry based on her Department's consultation on a future regulatory regime for the private security industry, published in September 2013.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39202","39202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522633","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Prevent coordinator posts have been advertised in each of the last five years; and what the average number of applications received for those posts was.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39185","39185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522634","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to implement the family reunification process for unaccompanied children in Europe with family in the UK.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39184","39184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522635","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's press release, Unaccompanied asylum-seeking children to be resettled from Europe, published on 4 May 2016, what the timetable is for implementation of that commitment.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39195","39195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522636","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice, assistance and representation the Government provides to unsettled asylum-seeking women and children who have experienced gender-based violence.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39196","39196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522637","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service had been in process for more than 30 days in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39043","39043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522638","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications the Disclosure and Barring Service has processed in each week of the last six months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39044","39044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522639","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service took longer than 30 days to process in 2014-15.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39045","39045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522640","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to accelerate the family reunification process for unaccompanied children in Europe with family in the UK.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39085","39085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522641","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many deaths were caused by drink driving in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39038","39038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522642","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Adult First applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service are dealt with promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39042","39042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522643","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to assess how many people have had (a) offers of employment rescinded and (b) their employment terminated due to the time taken for Disclosure and Barring Service checks to be concluded.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39041","39041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522644","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what evidence can be provided to prove gross rental income in order to meet the minimum income threshold for a spousal visa.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39036","39036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522645","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a zero-tolerance policy for drink driving for commercial drivers in England and Wales.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38968","38968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522646","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will develop a coordinated refugee dispersal policy with (a) all nations of the UK, (b) other government departments and (c) local government incorporating the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme, the dispersal and transfer of unaccompanied children and the Compass Contracts for accommodation of asylum seekers.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38960","38960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522647","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has a target for when the time taken to process Disclosure and Barring Service applications for residents of Dulwich and West Norwood constituency will routinely be completed within 60 days or less.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38962","38962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522648","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding criteria are included in the terms and conditions of Compass Contracts awarded for providing accommodation to asylum seekers.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38972","38972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522649","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many interviews with people making accusations of child abuse have been carried out by Operation Pallial under the Achieving Best Evidence guidance.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39000","39000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522650","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many convictions have been secured under Operation Pallial; and how many people so convicted did not have any previous convictions for similar offences.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39001","39001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522651","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) total, (b) police, (c) CPS and (d) court costs of Operation Pallial have been to date.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39002","39002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522652","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that police forces have the necessary resources to tackle dealers of substances banned under the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39004","39004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522653","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass contracts for asylum accommodation, if she will publish (a) the codes of discipline that providers have in place pursuant to 1.2.9.2 of the Compass Statement of Requirements and (b) how many breaches of such codes took place in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38984","38984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522654","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass contracts for asylum accommodation, if she will publish (a) copies of the training programmes that providers have in place pursuant to 1.2.9.2 of the Compass Statement of Requirements and (b) the dates on which such training took place in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38985","38985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522655","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass contracts for asylum accommodation and paragraphs 4.4.2.6 (b), (d) and (e) of the Compass Statement of requirements, how many reports were made by service users in each Compass region of (a) anti-social, suspicious, criminal, threatening or harassing behaviour, (b) neglect, sexual harassment or exploitation and (c) domestic violence or concerns with safeguarding of children in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38986","38986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522656","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Compass contracts for asylum accommodation and paragraphs 4.5.1.3(d) and (e) of the Compass Statement of Requirements, how many reports were made by service users in each Compass region of (a) sexual or physical abuse and concerns regarding the safeguarding of children, neglect, harassment or exploitation and (b) theft or loss of a service user's belongings in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38987","38987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522657","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to which countries her Department returns people through the assisted voluntary return programme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39024","39024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522658","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many extraditions have been approved since 1990 in respect of which written assurances have been received that the death penalty will not be imposed.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39029","39029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522659","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the budget has been for the Ending Gang Violence and Exploitation Peer Review Network for each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39019","39019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522660","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) mean, (b) maximum and (c) median value was of refugee integration loans in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39222","39222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522661","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for a refugee integration loan have been (a) made, (b) accepted and (c) refused in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39221","39221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522662","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) mean, (b) maximum and (c) median length of time has been for a decision to be made on an application for a refugee integration loan in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39223","39223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522663","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to accelerate the family reunification process for unaccompanied children in Europe with family in the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39191","39191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522664","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the issuing of 30-day entry clearance visas does not inhibit refugee family reunion; and for what reasons such time-limited entry clearance visas are issued.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39205","39205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522665","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants for refugee family reunion have been made outside the immigration rules in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39206","39206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522666","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what way the provisions of the Modern Slavery Act 2016 will support child advocates.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39263","39263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522667","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase border security of the UK coast.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39244","39244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522668","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to support children trafficked from abroad.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39262","39262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522669","2016-06-07","Department for International Development","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the finding of the Concern Worldwide (UK) report of 20 May 2016, Still Paying the Price, on the proportion of funding pledged during the Supporting Syria and the Region Conference in February 2016 so far received, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that all pledges are being fulfilled.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39235","39235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522670","2016-06-07","Department for International Development","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its aid is spent appropriately and on those in greatest need.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39259","39259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522671","2016-06-07","Department for International Development","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the UK aid budget is spent on water and sanitation; how that proportion was decided; and if she will increase that proportion.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39210","39210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522672","2016-06-07","Department for International Development","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to assist people in Bangladesh to mitigate the effects of Cyclone Roanu.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39168","39168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522673","2016-06-07","Department for International Development","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help (a) women and (b) all people in Bangladesh affected by Cyclone Roanu.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39144","39144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522674","2016-06-07","Department for International Development","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help people in Bangladesh build resilience against future extreme weather events in (a) Chittagong and (b) Bangladesh.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39150","39150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522675","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many corporate bodies have been prosecuted under the Bribery Act 2010.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39162","39162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522676","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what procedure over what period findings of Not Guilty are entered into the Criminal Record database.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39142","39142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522677","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the needs of (a) the old, (b) the very young, (c) people with difficulties with IT literacy, (d) people with difficulties with literacy and (c) other vulnerable groups are provided for in digital courts.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39165","39165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522678","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how his Department plans to fund the investment in ICT required to modernise and digitalise the court service.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39164","39164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522679","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what type of (a) indictable and (b) violence against the person offences were committed by offenders who participated in an out-of-court restorative justice resolution in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39175","39175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522680","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) out-of-court restorative justice resolutions and (b) cautions were given to (i) people on suspended prison sentences and (ii) prisoners released on licence in the latest year for which information is held.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39173","39173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522681","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have participated in an out-of-court restorative justice resolution on more than one occasion.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39174","39174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522682","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of participation in out-of-court restorative justice on reoffending rates.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39176","39176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522683","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to place the offences committed by offenders who participate in out-of-court restorative justice on the Police National Computer and make them available to courts dealing with any future offending.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39177","39177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522684","2016-06-08","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total amount (a) awarded and (b) recovered was from individuals convicted of human trafficking offences in each of the last three years; and how much of the money so recovered was allocated to (i) the Treasury, (ii) the police and (iii) the victim.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39098","39098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522685","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37128, what the average cost is of a First-tier Tribunal (Social Entitlement Chamber) appeal hearing.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39104","39104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522686","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claims to compensate victims of human trafficking have been lodged with the Criminals Injuries Compensation Authority in each of the last three years; and how much has been paid in compensation to victims of human trafficking in that time.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39099","39099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522687","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) victims in criminal human trafficking cases were awarded compensation by the trial judge and (b) convicted human traffickers were ordered to pay compensation to their victims by the trial judge in each of the last three years; what the value was of the award or order in each such case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39101","39101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522688","2016-06-08","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value is of legal aid paid to enable victims of human trafficking to bring claims of compensation against their traffickers since the Modern Slavery Act 2015 came into force; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39100","39100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522689","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of claims of equal pay to employment tribunals in 2015 were successful for (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39023","39023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522690","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made since the Law Commission's consultation and proposals regarding logbook loans; and what steps the Government has taken to review the Bills of Sale Act 1878.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39028","39028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522691","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many current prison inmates have been diagnosed with dementia.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38998","38998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522692","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many professional enablers have been sanctioned in the last 12 months for facilitating the laundering of corrupt assets.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39207","39207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522693","2016-06-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many equal pay claims accepted by employment tribunals in 2015 had been made against (a) government departments, (b) non-departmental public bodies and (c) local authorities.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39241","39241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522694","2016-06-07","Prime Minister","2016-06-03","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to 10 Downing Street; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38963","38963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522695","2016-06-07","Scotland Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on steps to tackle ticket touting.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38956","38956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522696","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to ensure that (a) Northern Ireland and (b) other parts of the UK benefit from transport infrastructure improvements.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38954","38954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522697","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 27 April 2016 to Question 34680, if he will provide an update on his Department's work through the EU and the European Aviation Safety Agency on developing safety rules for drones; and whether his Department holds information on the number of other EU member states which already have registration systems for drones.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39003","39003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522698","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37788, what estimate he has made of the overall cost to the public purse in the last Parliament of his Department's work on the consideration of the potential site for a UK spaceport.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39012","39012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522699","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37520, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of industrial action on the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern rail franchise since that franchise came into operation.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39013","39013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522700","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on rail services per head of population in each region of England in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39009","39009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522701","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in which month he expects the Greater Anglia rail franchise to be awarded.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38994","38994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522702","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in which month he expects the new arrangements for rail passenger refunds following delays to be announced.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38995","38995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522703","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37865, on large goods vehicles, when he expects officials of his Department to report to him on steps to improve the provision and quality of roadside facilities.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39078","39078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522704","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to implement the recommendations of his Department's Trust Port Study, published on 26 May 2016; and what steps he plans to take to support parliamentary scrutiny of that implementation.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39077","39077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522705","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value is of Network Rail's traffic management first deployment contract covering the Wales Rail Operating Centre and the Romford Rail Operating Centre; what the commissioning dates are for the two traffic management systems under that contract; and when the full integrated traffic management functionality for each location will be available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39089","39089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522706","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 12 May to Question 36843, which reviews of which transport infrastructure projects the Cabinet Secretary has participated in since his appointment to that role.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39096","39096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522707","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to recommendation 9 of his Department's Trust Port Study, published on 26 May 2016, what (a) guidance and (b) additional assistance his Department plans to provide to trust ports for periodic reviews of their model.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39076","39076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522708","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has commissioned or undertaken on the safety of LED lights and other new technologies as a replacement for cat's eyes on roads.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39082","39082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522709","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26794, when he plans to launch the new Access fund.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39095","39095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522710","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37870, whether the figures for his Department's spending on cycling programmes are in real terms.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39159","39159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522711","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37869, whether the figures for his Department's spending on walking programmes are in real terms.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39160","39160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522712","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will include a requirement in the Bus Services Bill for all new buses to be talking buses.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39166","39166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522713","2016-06-08","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37456, how the conversion of the West Coast Main Line Class 801 units to bi-mode diesel operation will be funded; and how his Department will recover such conversion costs.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39128","39128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522714","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason his Department does not include bus occupants as a road user type in its quarterly road casualty statistics.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39214","39214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522715","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to make buses more environmentally friendly.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39212","39212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522716","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason his Department does not collect and publish data on the number of different types of buses operating in England.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39213","39213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522717","2016-06-07","Department for Transport","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to make it a legal requirement for cyclists to wear helmets.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39220","39220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522718","2016-06-07","Home Office","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 26 May 2016, Official Report, column 682, how many women she was referring to when she stated that very few pregnant women were detained for immigration purposes.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39138","39138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522719","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 4 May 2016 to Question 35354, for what reasons the correspondence does not inform claimants of the availability of the Flexible Support Fund.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39122","39122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522720","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many referrals to debt advice services have been made by jobcentre staff in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39119","39119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522721","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the allocation for the Flexible Support Fund is lower in 2016-17 than in 2015-16.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39120","39120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522722","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 4 May 2016 to Question 35718, what his Department's combined legal costs were for the cases EE/2013/0145, EA2013/0148 and EA/2013/0149 heard at the First Tier Tribunal on 22 February 2016.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39121","39121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522723","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of self-employed people who have private pensions made state pension contributions in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39153","39153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522724","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 38312, if he will provide details of the relevant legislative criteria for payment of child maintenance to carers of children looked after under a special guardianship order.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39129","39129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522725","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people currently carrying out personal independence payment assessments are healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39113","39113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522726","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was that prospective employment and support allowance claimants waited between application and a decision on their claim being reached in the last three months.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39171","39171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522727","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have been sanctioned since 2010 in each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39066","39066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522728","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disability living allowance claimants have been sanctioned due to inability to attend a personal independence payments assessment since the introduction of such payments.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39065","39065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522729","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount is of child maintenance debt owed to parents with care.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39097","39097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522730","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with Ministers of the Northern Ireland Executive on the introduction of personal independence payments in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39112","39112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522731","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what medical qualifications are required for people carrying out assessments for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39110","39110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522732","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will  publish the timetable by area of planned migration of benefits for people in receipt of disability living allowance to personal independence payments.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39114","39114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522733","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which parliamentary constituencies individuals reside who have been subject to migration of benefits from disability living allowance to personal independence payments.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39111","39111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522734","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government has changed the Access to Work policy affecting disabled people who derive some of their income as part-time or full-time professional foster carers.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39143","39143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522735","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been migrated on to universal credit through a change of circumstance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39118","39118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522736","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a dedicated Deaf and Disability Careers Advisory Service.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38949","38949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522737","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people had their trivial commutation of their occupational pension request granted since the announcement of recent changes to pension regulations; and how many such requests have been refused due to the value of a pension exceeding £30,000.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39027","39027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522738","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support is available to a welfare recipient with a medical condition once a sanction has been imposed.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39032","39032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522739","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what account is taken of medical conditions when deciding whether to apply benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39033","39033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522740","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment appeals his Department has conceded prior to their being heard at first-tier tribunals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39021","39021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522741","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has responded to the report of the Royal College of Psychiatrists Commission on Acute Adult Psychiatric Care.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39030","39030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522742","2016-06-07","Department of Health","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address the shortages of acute adult psychiatric beds in England.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39031","39031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522743","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to produce child poverty statistics at (a) local authority and (b) parliamentary constituency level.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39018","39018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522744","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether jobseekers in receipt of universal credit are sanctioned if they do not look for work for 35 hours a week in every week of the year.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39227","39227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522745","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether jobseekers in receipt of universal credit are expected to look for work for 35 hours in a week in which Christmas falls.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39226","39226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522746","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on halving the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39237","39237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522747","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the receipts to the public purse were from (a) the £20 fee charged for applications to the Child Maintenance Service (CMS), (b) the 20 per cent collection fee for paying parents using the CMS collect and pay service, (c) the four per cent collection fee for receiving parents using the CMS collect and pay service and (d) enforcement fees levied on paying parents in 2015-16.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39238","39238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522748","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the outcomes were of the universal credit in-work conditionality pilots.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39239","39239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522749","2016-06-07","HM Treasury","2016-06-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress the Government has made on steps to introduce a pensions dashboard by 2019.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39240","39240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522750","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) maximum and (b) minimum rates are at which people must repay hardship payments when their universal credit claim restarts after a sanction.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39224","39224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522751","2016-06-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government has taken to prevent cliff edge effects in its policy on the equalisation of the state pension.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39234","39234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/522752","2016-06-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether jobseekers in receipt of universal credit are expected to look for work for 35 hours a week while they are on holiday.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39225","39225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521930","2016-06-06","Attorney General","2016-05-26","To ask the Attorney General, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from the Law Officers' Departments circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38810","38810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521931","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38809","38809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521932","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the average effect on graduates (a) student loan repayments and (b) student loan balance of the changes to the loan repayment threshold announced in the 2015 Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38722","38722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521933","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the evidence by the Federation of Small Businesses to the National Minimum Wage Low Pay Commission Report Spring 2016, page 244, on age discrimination in recruitment.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38726","38726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521934","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38765","38765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521935","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on plans to sell off student loans; and what recent estimate he has made of the amount of revenue expected to be raised by that sell off.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38764","38764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521936","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 17 January 2014 to Question 183346, how much of the Economic and Social Research Council budget was allocated to research on health and safety matters in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38751","38751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521937","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to section 4 of the Trade Union Act 2016, when he plans to commission an independent review of electronic balloting; and which organisations he plans to consult before preparing his response to that review.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38758","38758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521938","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what interest has accrued on student loans taken out in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38908","38908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521939","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many civil servants currently working for the Government have been involved in negotiating trade deals over the last 20 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38835","38835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521940","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new companies were started in Stafford constituency in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38837","38837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521941","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what date in June 2016 the UK's public central register of company beneficial ownership will be launched.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38860","38860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521942","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how his Department assesses differences in productivity levels between workers aged under and over 25.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38627","38627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521943","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons the Director of the Social Market Foundation was recommended as the independent member of the selection board which will advise  him on the appointment of the Chair of the Teaching Excellence Framework Panel.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38615","38615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521944","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what comparative assessment he has made of productivity levels of workers aged under and over 25 in the (a) hospitality and (b) retail sectors; and what account is taken of such productivity data in determining the level of the National Minimum Wage.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38628","38628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521945","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish a detailed timeline for the introduction of the apprenticeship levy to assist small and medium-sized enterprises to develop future apprentice and training plans.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38634","38634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521946","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that young people who receive summer assessment results in September (a) 2017 and (b) 2018 will have improved prospects of securing an apprenticeship as a result of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38635","38635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521947","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with nursing care providers on the number of clinical placements available for nursing students.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38642","38642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521948","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of ending the NHS bursary system on (a) female, (b) BME, and (c) older students.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38641","38641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521949","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of businesses which were bankrupted as a result of late payment of invoices.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38663","38663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521950","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answers of 19 April 2016 to Questions 34108, 34137 and 34138, when the data on overseas and UK-based ownership of property will be placed in the Library.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38680","38680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521951","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to inform students with existing student loans of the (a) changes announced to the loan repayment threshold in the 2015 Autumn Statement and (b) effect of those changes on their student loan balance and repayments.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38699","38699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521952","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the TUC's oral evidence to the National Minimum Wage Low Pay Commission Report Spring 2016, page 242, on the rate of labour market improvement for those aged between 21 and 24.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38727","38727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521953","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on the British automotive industry.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38898","38898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521954","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the quality of information provided to potential students before they apply for a student loan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38907","38907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521955","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of staff of (a) his Department (b) the Research Councils, (c) the Skills Funding Agency, (d) the Insolvency Service, (e) UK Shared Business Services Limited, (f) Innovate UK and (g) the Student Loans Company are (i) female and (ii) from an ethnic minority.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38922","38922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521956","2016-06-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 1 March 2016 to Question 28171, what rules will apply to use of the reading room for hon. Members for classified documents relating to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership; whether access will be limited to Members of both Houses; and when he plans to write to hon. Members to confirm how they can access and use those documents.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38925","38925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521957","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants are paid through limited companies in each Government department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38936","38936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521958","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans for the Anti-Corruption Innovation Hub to have any full-time staff.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38870","38870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521959","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a list of all public appointments approved by Ministers of his Department since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38921","38921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521960","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to launch the Anti-Corruption Innovation Hub.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38871","38871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521961","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to introduce a conviction check process to prevent corrupt bidders from winning public contracts.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38866","38866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521962","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government officials have been allocated to help establish the new International Anti-Corruption Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38868","38868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521963","2016-06-06","Home Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress the Government has made on assisting the Egmont group to establish a Centre of Excellence for Financial Intelligence Units.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38880","38880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521964","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has begun its IMF Fiscal Transparency Evaluation.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38879","38879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521965","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Inter-Ministerial Group on Corruption has met since 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38864","38864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521966","2016-06-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether a timetable has been agreed for the Overseas Territories and Crown dependencies to establish central registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38865","38865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521967","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with which countries the Government is working to establish the International Anti-Corruption Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38867","38867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521968","2016-06-06","Department for Transport","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Government spent on vehicles for (a) Ministers and (b) Senior Civil Servants in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38892","38892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521969","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff were (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff in each government department from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38790","38790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521970","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether a timetable has been agreed for setting up the new International Anti-Corruption Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38849","38849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521971","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has allocated any funding for setting up the new International Anti-Corruption Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38850","38850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521972","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) structure and (b) timetable has been established for the Government's consideration of the Chilcot Report.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38695","38695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521973","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what format the Government's response to the Chilcot Report will be made public.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38696","38696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521974","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what provision will be made for helping veterans and their families who may be affected by the publication of the Chilcot Report.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38697","38697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521975","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a programme which provides legal recognition for a year of full-time voluntary service by young people similar to such programmes operating in the US, Germany and France.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38621","38621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521976","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether provisions will be made as part of the planned National Citizen Service Bill to create a new legal status to recognise those participating in full-time long-term volunteering programmes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38620","38620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521977","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a list of all invitees to the Anti-Corruption Summit held on 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38856","38856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521978","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's policy is on providing early sight of the Chilcot Inquiry report to injured veterans of the Iraq Conflict.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38875","38875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521979","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will remove the restriction that prohibits the publication of official government documents relating to the contaminated blood scandal under the 100-year rule.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38754","38754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521980","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date he plans to publish official government documents relating to contaminated blood that are held under the 100-year rule.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38755","38755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521981","2016-06-06","Department of Health","2016-05-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many official government documents are held under the 100-year rule relating to the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38757","38757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521982","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which members of the Inter-Ministerial Group on Corruption attended the Tackling Corruption Together conference held on 11 May 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38873","38873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521983","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which members of the Inter-Ministerial Group on Corruption attended the Anti-Corruption Summit on 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38874","38874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521984","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidelines there are for measuring the performance of contractors delivering public services.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38760","38760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521985","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy that questions to determine the number of veterans, armed forces personnel and reservists be included in the next census.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38748","38748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521986","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria are used to decide whether people are fit and proper persons to engage with Government as directors of companies or not-for-profit ventures.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38698","38698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521987","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the amount spent on non-payroll staff in the Government Digital Service in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38804","38804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521988","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-payroll staff were hired by each government department in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38805","38805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521989","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much was spent from the public purse on non-payroll staff in all government departments in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38806","38806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521990","2016-06-06","Cabinet Office","2016-05-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38811","38811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521991","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's news story of 10 April 2016, UK launches cross-government taskforce on the Panama Papers, (a) how many leads the multi-agency taskforce is currently investigating and (b) how many of those leads have a direct link to the leaked documents relating to the operations of Mossack Fonseca.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38724","38724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521992","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the report, Tackling Tax Fraud, published by the National Audit Office in December 2015, how much of the tax revenue at stake for successful prosecutions in each range in Table 16 was recovered.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38713","38713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521993","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 May 2016 to Question 37198, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK have been returned to his Department; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38780","38780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521994","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library copies of all letters, leaflets and other material from his Department circulated to (a) stakeholders and (b) members of the public on the EU Referendum; what the costs of the production and distribution of that material has been since 1 January 2016; and what he estimates the cost of any further production and distribution of such material will be between 6 May 2016 and 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38828","38828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521995","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any of the staff of the cross-agency taskforce examining the Panama Papers are working only on that taskforce.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38872","38872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521996","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing an additional rate of stamp duty on property purchases by foreign investors.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38852","38852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521997","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on business and investor confidence of potential retroactive changes being made to (a) Enterprise Investment Schemes, (b) Venture Capital Trusts and (c) other investment incentives.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38857","38857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521998","2016-06-06","HM Treasury","2016-05-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to HM Revenue and Custom's publication Statistics on recently arrived non-UK EEA nationals subject to income tax and National Insurance contributions or receiving HMRC administered benefits of May 2016, how many child benefit claims of what amount were made by (a) non-UK EEA nationals and (b) recently arrived non-UK EEA nationals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 38889","38889"
